in this tutorial we'll be going over how
在本教程中，我们将介绍如何
you can rasterize Vector objects in
可以在中栅格化矢量对象
inkscape more importantly though we'll
Inkscape更重要的是，我们将
be going over why you would want to do
仔细研究你为什么想要做
such a thing so let's get started here
这样的事情，让我们从这里开始吧
on my canvas I have this example design
在我的画布上，我有这个样例设计
which consists of individual Vector
它由单个向量组成
elements if I zoom in on this you can
元素如果我放大这个，你可以
see there's no quality loss
你看，没有质量损失
if I wanted to make a rasterized or a
如果我想要制作光栅化的或
pixel based copy of this design here all
此设计的基于像素的复制在此全部
I have to do is Select it and go to edit
我要做的就是选择它并进入编辑
and select make a bitmap copy
并选择制作位图副本
and when you do that it creates a copy
当您这样做时，它会创建一个副本
of your selection only it's a pixel
所选内容中只有一个像素
based copy so if I zoom in on this you
基于副本，所以如果我放大这张图
can see this is indeed a pixel based
可以看出这确实是基于像素的
image
图像
now let's have a look at an example of
现在让我们来看一个例子
when this sort of thing would be useful
这类东西什么时候会有用
so on my screen here I have this
在我的屏幕上，我看到了这个
halftone pattern that we created in a
半色调图案，我们在
previous tutorial and this actually
以前的教程和这个实际上
serves as a perfect example of when to
是一个完美的例子，说明了何时
use this sort of thing because this
使用这种东西是因为这
design here consists of hundreds maybe
这里的设计可能有数百个
even thousands of tiny little circles
即使是数以千计的小圆圈
and because of that the software has to
正因如此，软件必须
process the information of each and
处理每个和的信息
every one of these elements which can
这些元素中的每一个都可以
slow down the software and decrease
降低软件的运行速度并降低
performance so this is where making a
所以这就是制作一个
bitmap copy comes in handy because it
位图复制很方便，因为它
allows you to create a pixel based copy
允许您创建基于像素的副本
which will free up a lot of CPU usage
这将释放大量的CPU使用量
and make the software run a lot better
并让软件运行得更好
so what I'm going to do is I'm going to
所以我要做的是我要
open my layers menu I'm going to come up
打开我的层菜单，我会弹出
here to layers and select layers and
此处为层并选择层和
objects
对象
and I'm going to look for
我要去找一个
here we go Layer Two this is where all
我们开始第二层，这就是所有
of the objects remain on this layer I'm
保留在这一层上的物体，我
going to select the objects I want to
要选择我想要的对象
make a copy of
复制…的副本
and if I go to edit and select make a
如果我去编辑并选择Make a
bitmap copy we now have an image over
位图复制我们现在有了一幅图像
here in the layers menu so I'm going to
在这里的层菜单中，所以我要
take this image and I'm going to pop it
拍下这张照片，我就把它拍下来
out of the layer and place it on top of
从层中取出并将其放在
the layer and if I scroll up you can see
这一层，如果我向上滚动，你可以看到
it up there and then I'm going to
它在上面，然后我要去
collapse the layer
塌陷层
and I'm going to lock the layer and turn
我要锁定这一层，然后转身
off the visibility of the layer and now
关闭该层的可见性，现在
we have just this pixel based image here
我们这里只有这张基于像素的图像
and now the software is already running
现在这个软件已经在运行了
much smoother if I try doing this and
如果我试着这样做会流畅得多
working with this with thousands of
与数以千计的
individual little elements being
个别的小元素是
displayed on the screen it's going to
它将显示在屏幕上
decrease performance by a lot now one
性能现在大幅降低1
problem you may encounter when doing
你在做的时候可能会遇到的问题
this sort of thing if I zoom in here you
如果我把你的照片放大
can see the resolution isn't too great
可以看到分辨率不是太高
so if you want to make bitmap copies
因此，如果您想制作位图副本
while preserving a higher resolution
同时保持较高的分辨率
than what the default is what I would
比起缺省值，我会
recommend doing is going into inkscape
推荐的做法是进入Inkscape
preferences if you're a Windows or Linux
如果您是Windows或Linux用户，请选择首选项
User it's up here in the edit menu and
用户，它在编辑菜单中，并且
come down here to where it says either
到这里来，上面写着
preferences or inkscape preferences if
首选项或Inkscape首选项，如果
you're using Mac just come over here to
你在用Mac，快过来
where it says inkscape and select
其中显示为Inkscape，然后选择
settings
设置
and in the menu what we're looking for
在菜单上我们要找的是
is over here where it says imported
就在这里，上面写着进口的
images I'm going to come down here to
我接下来要来这里的图片
where it says resolution for create a
其中显示了创建
bitmap copy the default is 96. I'm going
位图复制默认为96。我要走了
to change that to 300. and then close
将这一数字改为300。然后关闭
out of the menu and now next time when
不在菜单上，现在下一次
you make a bitmap copy it'll be a much
你制作一个位图副本，这将是一个很大的
higher resolution so let me show you
更高的分辨率，让我展示给你看
here as an example let me get rid of my
这里作为一个例子，让我去掉我的
other copy and let me make a new copy
另一份，让我复制一份新的
of my halftones here I'm going to select
在我这里的半色调中，我将选择
all of my halftones
我所有的半色调
I'll go to edit make a bitmap copy
我要去编辑制作一个位图副本
take the image layer pop that out
把图像层弹出来
collapse the layer
塌陷层
turn this off
把这个关掉
and there we go this is a much higher
我们走吧，这是一个更高的
resolution like I'm zooming in Beyond
分辨率就像我在放大更远
100 and you don't see any pixelation yet
100，你还看不到任何像素化
in fact I could zoom in quite a bit
事实上，我可以放大相当多。
without any kind of pixelation
没有任何类型的像素化
whatsoever I have to go pretty far there
不管怎么说，我要走得很远。
before you start seeing the pixelation
在开始看到像素之前
so that's a little tip that you can use
这是您可以使用的一个小技巧
to help create higher resolution copies
帮助创建更高分辨率的副本
of your rasterize objects if you found
如果您发现的话，您的网格对象
this lesson useful then consider
这堂课很有用，然后考虑一下
checking out my inkscape master class
查看我的水墨风景大师班
it's a collection of over 60 videos
它包含60多个视频
where I go over all of the tools and
我会检查所有工具，
features in inkscape and I explain what
水墨景观中的特征，我解释了什么
they are and demonstrate how they work
它们是并演示它们如何工作
kind of like how I did in this video we
有点像我在这个视频中所做的那样，
even have a private Community where you
甚至有一个私人社区，您可以在其中
can ask questions and get help from me
可以向我提出问题并寻求帮助
anytime you want and best of all there's
任何时候您想要的，最重要的是，有
no monthly membership fees you just pay
只需支付每月会员费
17 one time and you're in for Life I'll
17一次，你就会终生难忘我会
have some information about that down
有一些相关信息
below if you want to check that out as
如果您想检查一下，请在下面作为
always thanks for watching
始终感谢观看
[Music]
[音乐]
thank you
谢谢你